BISIKHA SUBEDI

9843067830 | bisikhasubedi26@gmail.com | Lokanthali-01, Bhaktapur

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bisikha-subedi-94b295158

Professional Summary

I am an energetic and an optimist preparing myself for a career change. I have been working as an Assistant Lecturer in an engineering college and with the passion and drive to get more out of my academic earnings, I am working hard on my technical skills. As a graduate with two years of working experience, I am a good learner with commendable communication skills and an excellent team player.

Employment history

- → WordPress Support Team Intern at WEN Solutions Pvt. Ltd
 - ◆ July, 2018 September, 2018
 - ♦ 3 months
- → WordPress Support Representative at WEN Solutions Pvt. Ltd
 - ♦ 5th October, 2018 to 15 October, 2019
 - ♦ 1 year
- → Assistant Lecturer at Lalitpur Engineering College
 - ◆ 14th November, 2019 till today

Education

→	Advanced College of Engineering and Management	2014 - 2018
	Bachelor's in Computer Engineering (BCT)First Division (66.91%)	
→	Himalayan Whitehouse International College, Tinkune	2012 – 2014
	+2 (Science - Physics)	
	◆ First Division (70.50%)	
→	Om Gyan Mandir Secondary School, Bhaktapur	2012 – 2014
	◆ School Leaving Certificate	
	◆ First Division with Distinction (85.63%)	

Skills & Abilities

- → Sound Knowledge of HTML5, CSS , javascript
- → Mediocre in frontend JS library React and Node js for backend development
- → Knowledge of version control system Git
- → Fluent in Nepali and English, both written and spoken
- → Friendly and easy going, thus, a very good team player.

Achievement

→ Co-Author of the Research paper published on IEEE-ICCIC 2018 conference.

Research Paper Title: Revolutionizing healthcare systems of developing country using Blockchain published on February, 2019

Reference:https://www.researchgate.net/publication/330778470_Rev olutionizing_healthcare_systems_of_a_developing_country_using_Bl ockchain

Projects Completed

- → Electronic Health Record System for immutable and safe data storage
 - ◆ Final Year Project
- → PI Router
 - ◆ Third Year Project
- → Water purity testing and notifying device and android application
 - ◆ Prototype made for the competition held by Robotics